Ralph E. Flanders Papers
Ralph E. Flanders Papers
- General correspondence files
  - General correspondence, 1934-1937
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers
      - Stetson, George (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - [General] (Box 18, Folder 6-10)
      - [General] (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
      - Minutes of, Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - American Society of Planning Officials (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - American Society of Tool Engineers, Buffalo (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - American Standards Association, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - American Standards Association, Sub Committee on Screw Threads (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - American Telephone & Telegraph Company (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - American Town Meeting on the Air (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Dewey A. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - The Annalist (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Applegate, C. Theodore (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Appleton, Mrs. Allen L. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - The Architectual Record (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Army Ordnance Association (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Associated Business Papers, Incorporated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Associated Press (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Association of Life Insurance Presidents (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Associated Industries of Vermont (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Atkinson, Kerr (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Atlantic Monthly (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Austin, Warren R. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Automobile Club of Vermont (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Ayres, Leonard P. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Baker, Charles Whiting (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bankers Club of America (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Banking (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Barnard, Chester L. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Barnes, N. W. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Barradas League & Gerald Barradas (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Batt, William L. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Beal, Henry S. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bavaj, Amor (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Beardslee, Martin (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Beaver Country Day School (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Beebe, C. D. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Belisle, Eugene (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Belknap, Roland W. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Belknap, Waldron P. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Bennington Evening Banner (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Berle, A. A. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Berresford, Arthur W. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Berry, George L. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Beggers, John D. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Bestrup, F. V. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Bliss, Collins P. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Bliss, Philip E. (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Blue Hill Observatory (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Boetcher, William J. H. (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Booker, Warren E. (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Boston Fire Department (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Boston & Maine Railroad (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Boston Ordnance District (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Boy Scouts (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Brady, Thomas (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Brattleboro Reformer (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Breckenridge, L. P. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Brennan, B. A. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Brentano's Book Stores (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Brewer & Stevens (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Brighman, Elbert S. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Brookings Institution (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Allan R. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Horace (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Brown, J. G. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Brown University (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Brown, W. W. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Brown & Sharpe Manufacturing Company (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Bryant, Mrs. Blanche B. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Buckingham, Earle C. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Buker, Henry (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Bullock, William E. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Burlington Free Press (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Burns, Eveline (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Burrage, William S. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Bush, S. P. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Business Advisory Council
      - [General] (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
      - Membership List (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Tax Committee (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - B, General (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Calder, John (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - California, University of (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Canfield, Mrs. Mary Grace (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Carpenter, Florence A. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Carter, Winthrop L. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Cassmore, Melvin W. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Central Statistical Board (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Central Vermont Railroad (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Chaffee, John S. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Chamberlain, Lawrence (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Champlain Valley Council (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Chapman, Ernest A. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Chapple, Joe Mitchell (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Chase, Charles (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Chase National Bank (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Chesterman, F. J. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Chicago Association of Commerce (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Club (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Chicago Daily News (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Chicago Tribune (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Chicago, University of (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Christian Science Monitor (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Christmas Letters Sent (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Churchill, W. L. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Cincinnati Chamber of Commerce (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Clark, Ernest L. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Clark, Evans, 20th Century Fund Incorporated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Clark, Evans, 20th Century Fund Incorporated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Clark, Evans, 20th Century Fund Incorporated, Corporation Study Reports (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Clausen, Leon R. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Clement, Charles S. & Company (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland Trust Company (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Cockrell, Ewing (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Codes, American Industry, National Recovery Administration (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Codex Graphic Chart Company (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Coes, Harold V. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Columbia University (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Cole, George (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Comings, Herbert B. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Commerce (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Commercial Investment Trust Corporation (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Economic Security (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Committee for the Nation (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Inquiry on Public Service Personnel (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Problems & Policy (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Community House (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Compton, Wilson (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Conference on Industrial Relations (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Congregational Board of Pastoral Supply (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Congregational and Christian Churches (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Congregational Church Men's Club (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Congregational Church, Vergennes, Vermont (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Conrad, P. W. (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Consumers Foundation Incorporated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Consumers Research Incorporated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Coolidge Memorial Corporation (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Coolidge, Marcus A. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Cornell University (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Courant, R. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Cowles Commission for Research (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Cox, Laurie Davidson (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Coyle, David Cushman (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Coyle, Grace L. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Crease, James (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Crockeet, A. E. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Crowther, Samuel (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Crusaders, Chicago, Illinois (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Crusaders of Connecticut (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Cummings, Homer S. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Cunningham, J. D. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Cutter, Victor M. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Czatt, Milton S. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Czerwonky, Hugo (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - C, General (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Dahl, G. K. (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Daniels, Mrs. Gertrude (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Dartmouth College (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Davenport, William S. (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Davis, F. B. Jr. (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Davis, Mrs. Gilbert Frankling (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Day, Mrs. George P. (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Dayton News (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Deane, Albert L. (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Democratic National Committee (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Dennison, Henry S. (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Dickerman, William C. (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Dickinson, E. T. (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Dickinson, H. C. (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Dickinson, Howard W. (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Dickinson, John C. (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Doerflinger, Chester A. (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Donham, Richard (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Donham, Wallace Brett (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Doolittle, H. L. (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Draper, Ernest (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Dreifus, Charles Jr. (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Dreyfus, Edwin D. (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Dunbar, Edith Flanders (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Dunn and Bradstreet (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Dunn, Gano (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - DuPont, E. I. de Nemours & Company (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Durable Goods Industries Committee (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Duryea, Charles E. (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - D, General (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Eastman, Lucius R. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Eberhardt, Frank E. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Eccles, Marriner S. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Econometric Society (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Economic Conference on Inflation (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Economic Forum, A Magazine of Politics, Finance, Industry (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Edie, Lionel D. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Elbert, Robert G. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Electrical Salvage Company (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Electrical World (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Ellis, Karl H. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Engineering Foundation (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Engineering Index, Incorporated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Engineering Institute of Canada (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Engineers Club of New York (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Engineers Club of Philadelphia (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Engineers Council for Professional Development (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Evans, Ernestine (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Evans, R. F. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Everett, Roberts (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Eye Clinic (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - E, General (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Fahey, John H. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Falk Foundation (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Farm Credit Administration (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Farmer, F. E. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Frank (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Federal Emergency Administration (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Federal Housing Administration (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Federal Mills Incorporated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Federal Power Commission (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Federal Reserve Bank (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Federated Church of Richmond, Vermont (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Feldman, Herman (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Fellows, E. R. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Fellows Gear Shaper (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Ferris, C. H. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Ferris, John P. (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Fields, Mr. Crosby (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Filene, Lincoln (Box 27, Folder 21-23)
    - Finch, Roy G. (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - First Congregational Church of Springfield, Vermont (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - First Roosevelt for President Club (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Fisher, Irving (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Fiske, David L. (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Fiske, Julian (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Fitch, Stanley G. H. (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Fitzpatrick, F. Stuart (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Foot, Harry W. (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Forbes Magazine (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Ford, Smith, P. (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Fort, Frank (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Forum (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Francis, James D. (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Franz, Frederick (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Freeman, John R. (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Friends World Conference Committee (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Fritz, John Metal Board of Award (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Fulweiler, W. H. (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - F, General (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Galloway, George B. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Gannett, Frank E. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Gardner, Eugene (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Garrett, E. H. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Gates, Benjamin (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Genealogical Quarterly (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - General Economic Council, Incorporated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - George School (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Georgia, University of (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Gibson, Ernest W. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Giddings, John T. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Giele, Walter S. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Gilfillan, Hobart (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Gilfillan, L. H. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Gill, John D. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Gould, Joseph D. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Gould, Norman (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Governor's Safety Council (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Graham, William J. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Gray, William R. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Greenfield Tap & Die Corporation (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Green Mountain Club, Incorporated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Green Mountain House Association (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Green, William (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Greensfelder, A. P. (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Groves, J. M. (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Gunnarson, A. B. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Gushee, Edward T. (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - G, General (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Haake, A. P. (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Hahn, Lew (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Hall, James A. (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Hammond, Charles S. (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Hanley, William A. (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Hanauer, H. J. (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Hannum, J. E. (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Hard, William (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Harper's & Brothers (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Harriman, Henry I. (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Harriman, W. A. (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Harris, E. T. (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Harris & Ewing, Incorporated (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Harrison, Albert (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Harrison, Robert E. W. (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Harvard University (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Harvard, Yale, Princeton Conference (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Harwood, E. C. (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Hasslinger, Hans Baron (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Hatch, Willard (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Hatfield, Charles (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Haus Motor Company Incorporated (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Heacock, B. C. (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Heimann, Henry H. (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Heitkamp, Frederick B. (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Henn, Edwin C. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Hettinger, A. J. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Heyniger, C. Lambert (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Hildreth, E. L. & Company (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Hillman, John Adams (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Hines, Herbert Henry (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Hirshfeld, C. F. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - (Mary) Hitchcock Hospital (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Hobart, Newton (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Hodges, Wetmore (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Holden, Arthur J. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Holman, Charles W. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Holton, Campbell (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - (Charles) Hook Committee (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Hook, Charles R. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Hook, James W. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Hopkins, Harry (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Horne, Donald (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Horne, George A. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Hough, Ulysses B. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - House of Representatives, United States (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Houston, George H. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Houston, Herbert S. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Howard, Florence Comstock (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Howe, Philip Oscar (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Hubbard, Grey (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Hughes, John R. (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Hughes, Orrin B. (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Humphreys, C. H. (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Humphreys, Mrs. R.N. (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Hunsaker, Mrs. Jerome C. (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Hunt, Omar S. (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Hunter, Roy (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Hurd, Archibald (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - H, General (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Ickes, Harold L. (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Independent Coalition of American Women (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Industrial Advisory Board (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Public Affairs (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - International Chamber of Commerce (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - International Committee of Young Men Christian Associations (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - International Correspondence School (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - International Management Congress of New York (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - International Industrial Relations Institute (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Interstate Committee of Conflicting Taxation, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - International Management Congress, Committee on Production (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Invitation, Prairie du Chien Woolen Mills Company (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Iowa State College (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Iowa, University of (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Irving Trust Company (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - I, General (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Jenson, Willard E. (Box 31, Folder 1-7)
    - Jones, Sullivan W. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Julian, Mrs. Charles (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Julian, William A. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - J, General (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Karsten, Karl (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Keagy, Walter R. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Kelley, Walter Stuart (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Kellogg, Paul U. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Kendall, Harry P. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Kenney, William P. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Kerr, Rev. Archibald (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Kettering, Charles F. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Kin-O-Lux, Incorporated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Klepesta, Josepf (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Kountze, de Lancey (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Koyemann, M. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Kurn Hattin Homes (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Kuthe, H. C. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - K, General (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Lauer, Conrad N. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Lavis, Fred (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Lawrence and Wheeler (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Leavitt, J. E. (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Lee, Irving S. (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Leeds, Morris E. (Box 32, Folder 25-27)
    - Lehigh University (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Leica Equipment (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Lewis, Mrs. Sinclair (Dorothy Thompson) (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Life Extension Institute (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Lincoln, James F. (Arc Welding Foundation) (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Lind, Herman, H. (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Litchfield, Paul W. (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Locke, Allen S. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Lombard, Norman (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Low, Fred R. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lowell Institute School (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Lumber Code, National Recovery Administration (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Lund, Robert L. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Luten, David B. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Lybrand, Ross, Brothers & Montgomery (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - L, General (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Machinery & Allied Products Institute (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Main, Charles T. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mallery, Otto T. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Manufacturers Record (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Marquis Company (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Marshall, Oscar (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Marsteller, H. T. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Martin, Fred C. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Martin, Thomas W. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts Commission Unemployment Insurance (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 33, Folder 20-21)
    - Mathews, Joseph F. (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - May, Mark A. (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Maccoull, Neil (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - MacCoy, W. Logan (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - MacFadden, Bernarr (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - MacFarlane, W. G. (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - MacLennan, James F. (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - McCall, Chester H. (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - McCullough, Hall Park (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - McDonald, Frederick H. (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - McGraw, Hill Book Company (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - McGregor, A. G. (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - McInnerney, Thomas H. (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - McKenna, Charles M. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Mead, George H. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Melendy, Emery A. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Mensing, Frederick D. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Meredith, L. Douglas (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Merritt, Joseph (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Meyer, Eugene (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Michener, C. D. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Midday Club (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Middlebury College (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Milk Recommendation Committee, Report of (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Millar, Preston S. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Joseph (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Millett, William H. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Millis, Harry A. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Mills, Frederick C. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Minneapolis Civic & Commerce Association (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Mitchell, Karl M. (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Mitchell, Wesley C. (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Mohler, John R. (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Montague, Gilbert (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Moody, Walter S. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Mooney, James D. (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Moore, W. Clement (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Morpeth, Rachel M. (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Morris, Robert H. (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Morton, Sterling (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Moshassyck Cemetery Corporation (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Motor Vehicle Department of Vermont (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Moulton, Harold G. (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Moultrop, Irving (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Muller, Alfred (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Munsell, A.E.O. (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Murphy, Elijah D. (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Myers, W.I. (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Myrick, Rawson, C. (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - M, General (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Nation (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Manufacturers (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - National City Bank of New York (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - National Consumer News (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - National Economic and Social Planning Council (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - National Economic Council (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - National Geographic Magazine (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - National Industry Conference Board (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - National Industrial Conference (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - National Life Insurance (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - National Life Insurance Company (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - National Management Council (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - National Monetary Conference (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - The National Party (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - National Policy Committee (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - National Recovery Administration (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - National Resources Board (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - National Retail Dry Goods Association (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - National Shawmut Bank of Boston (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - National Society of Professional Engineers (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - National Youth Administration (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Nation's Business (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Nation's Commerce (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Nebraska, University of (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Nevada, University of (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - New England Council (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - New England Power Company (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - New England Public Service Corporation (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - New England Regional Planning Committee (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - New Hampshire Commission on Unemployment Reserves (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - New Hampshire State Planning & Development Commission (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - New Hampshire, State of (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Newman, Douglas (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Newsboy World (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - New York Herald Tribune (Box 37, Folder 10)